{
    "subject": "resource/Summer_of_'42",
    "predicate": "property/language",
    "object": "English",
    "human_readable": "The language of 'Summer of '42' is English.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9505986571311951,
            "question": "Is 'Summer of '42' an English-language film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7999034523963928,
            "question": "Is there any dialogue in other languages besides English in 'Summer of '42'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7822818756103516,
            "question": "Can you understand the movie 'Summer of '42' if you only speak English?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7534216642379761,
            "question": "What language would you need to understand to watch 'Summer of '42'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7502061128616333,
            "question": "What language was 'Summer of '42' filmed in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7250487804412842,
            "question": "In what language is the movie 'Summer of '42' primarily spoken?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6750054359436035,
            "question": "Does the movie 'Summer of '42' use English dialogue?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6689884662628174,
            "question": "What language is used in the screenplay for 'Summer of '42'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.41287484765052795,
            "question": "Is 'Summer of '42' a foreign film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4014497399330139,
            "question": "Would subtitles be necessary to watch 'Summer of '42'?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The language of 'Summer of '42' is English.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5725_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is 'Summer of '42' a foreign film?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5725_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What language is used in the screenplay for 'Summer of '42'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5725_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does the movie 'Summer of '42' use English dialogue?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5725_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5725_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5725_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5725_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5725_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5725_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5725_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5725_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5725_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5725_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5725_76.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in the form of a structured JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple that the language of \"Summer of '42\" is English, as mentioned in the product details for the DVD release (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_5725/re-ranker-msmarco/41.txt):\n\n\"Format: NTSC\n\nLanguage: English\"\n\nThis information confirms that the language of \"Summer of '42\" is indeed English."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\n**Explanation:** The documents mention that the film \"Summer of '42\" has an English title and is available in a version with English dialogue, supporting the statement that its language is English."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}